const ict = [
{
    question: "CPU stands for:",
    options: ["Central Process Unit", "Central Processing Unit", "Computer Personal Unit", "Control Process Unit"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "RAM is:",
    options: ["Permanent memory", "Temporary memory", "External storage", "Firmware"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "HTML is used for:",
    options: ["Programming", "Database", "Web structure", "Networking"],
    answer: 2
},
{
    question: "IP address identifies:",
    options: ["User", "Computer on network", "Website name", "Browser"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "Operating system example:",
    options: ["Windows", "CPU", "RAM", "Mouse"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Binary system uses:",
    options: ["0-9", "0 and 1", "1-10", "A-F"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "ROM is:",
    options: ["Editable memory", "Read-only memory", "Temporary memory", "Cache"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "LAN means:",
    options: ["Local Area Network", "Large Area Network", "Line Access Node", "Linked Access Network"],
    answer: 0
},
{
    question: "Compiler converts:",
    options: ["Machine to English", "High-level to machine code", "Binary to text", "Text to binary"],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "Database stores:",
    options: ["Music", "Videos", "Structured data", "Images only"],
    answer: 2
}
];